Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
I've been plotting for a thousand years.
لقد كنت أخطط لألف عام.
As long as I eliminate
طالما قمت بالقضاء
all you innkeepers today,
جميع أصحاب النزل اليوم،
the monster inn will disappear.
سوف يختفي نزل الوحش.
I will regain my freedom.
سأستعيد حريتي.
Shangguan Feiye,
شانجوان فيي,
Dongfang Zhaobai,
دونغفانغ تشاوباي,
all of you can die!
جميعكم يمكن أن تموتوا!
Ling Po,
لينغ بو،
you're celebrating too soon.
أنت تحتفل مبكرا جدا.
I almost forgot
لقد نسيت تقريبا
about you.
عنك.
Didn't you break ties with him?
ألم تقطع علاقتك به؟
You even planted the Wujian Vine on him.
حتى أنك زرعت عليه نبات Wujian Vine.
You wanted him to take Shangguan Feiye's place
لقد أردت منه أن يأخذ مكان شانغوان فيي
and die from the karmic fire.
ويموت من نار الكرمية.
I was indeed deceived by you at first.
لقد خدعتني حقا في البداية.
I mistakenly thought Shangguan Feiye killed my brother.
اعتقدت خطأً أن شانغوان فييي قتل أخي.
But later I remembered something.
ولكن بعد ذلك تذكرت شيئا.
It was you who told me
لقد كنت أنت الذي قلت لي
that evil spirits appeared in Shangguan Feiye's village.
ظهرت الأرواح الشريرة في قرية شانغوان فيي.
You sent me to catch those monsters.
لقد أرسلتني للقبض على هؤلاء الوحوش.
You wanted her to misunderstand
لقد أردتها أن تسيء فهمك
that I was Dongfang Zhaobai.
أنني كنت دونغفانغ Zhaobai.
That I killed her loved ones.
أنني قتلت أحبائها.
Then use her to eliminate my brother.
ثم استخدمها للقضاء على أخي.
It seems
يبدو أنه
you're not as stupid as I thought.
أنت لست غبيًا كما اعتقدت.
But aren't you afraid your brother
ولكن ألا تخاف من أخيك؟
might actually die from the Wujian Vine
قد يموت بالفعل من نبات Wujian Vine
filled with karmic fire?
مليئة بالنار الكرمية؟
How did the Wujian Vine end up on you?
كيف انتهى بك الأمر مع Wujian Vine؟
My brother and I
انا واخي
are incarnations of the Huangquan Jade.
هي تجسيدات ليشم هوانغكوان.
The Wujian Vine
كرمة ووجيان
connects the two jade pieces.
يربط قطعتي اليشم.
They can naturally be transferred between us.
ويمكن أن تنتقل بيننا بشكل طبيعي.
Karmic fire!
نار الكرمية!
So what if it's a different person?
فماذا لو كان شخصًا مختلفًا؟
Besides,
بجانب،
now you bear the power of karmic fire.
الآن أنت تحمل قوة النار الكرمية.
You'll soon be reduced to ashes.
سوف تتحول قريبا إلى رماد.
What can you possibly do?
ماذا يمكنك أن تفعل؟
It was all just an illusion to deceive you.
لقد كان كل هذا مجرد وهم لخداعك.
When you thought my brother
عندما فكرت أخي
was completely controlled by the Wujian Vine,
تم التحكم بها بالكامل بواسطة Wujian Vine،
I transferred it to myself.
نقلته إلى نفسي.
Of course,
بالطبع،
I was also gambling.
كنت أيضا مقامرًا.
Betting that Shangguan Feiye
الرهان على أن Shangguan Feiye
would risk her life
سوف تخاطر بحياتها
to return to a thousand years ago.
للعودة إلى ألف سنة مضت.
So what?
وماذا في ذلك؟
You're only half of the Huangquan Jade.
أنت نصف اليشم هوانغكوان فقط.
Now you bear the power of karmic fire.
الآن أنت تحمل قوة النار الكرمية.
You'll soon be reduced to ashes.
سوف تتحول قريبا إلى رماد.
As for those two,
أما بالنسبة لهذين الاثنين،
they're not even worth mentioning.
إنهم لا يستحقون حتى أن نذكرهم.
Is that so?
هل هذا صحيح؟
Today is the day you die.
اليوم هو اليوم الذي ستموت فيه.
Prepare to meet your end.
استعد للقاء نهايتك.
Qiongqi.
تشيونغكي.
The Huangquan Jade can only be restored
لا يمكن استعادة اليشم هوانغكوان إلا
to its original power when the two pieces are united.
إلى قوتها الأصلية عندما يتم اتحاد القطعتين.
Only then can we stop the Demon King.
حينها فقط يمكننا إيقاف ملك الشياطين.
Please be careful.
يرجى توخي الحذر.
Wait for my return.
انتظر عودتي
I'm back.
لقد عدت.
From today onwards,
من اليوم فصاعدا،
you belong to me.
أنت ملكي.
Feiye.
تين.
Is anybody there?
هل يوجد أحد هناك؟
Help me!
ساعدني!
Let the past
دع الماضي
be the past.
كن الماضي.
In the days ahead,
في الأيام القادمة،
take good care of yourself.
اعتني بنفسك جيدا.
Hey, the boss is back.
مهلا، لقد عاد الرئيس.
Boss,
رئيس،
you're up early today.
لقد استيقظت مبكرا اليوم.
You look very nice today.
أنت تبدو لطيفًا جدًا اليوم.
Boss.
رئيس.
Good morning, boss.
صباح الخير يا رئيس.
Boss,
رئيس،
at your service!
في خدمتكم!
Hello, boss.
مرحبا يا رئيس.
All right.
حسنًا.
Boss,
رئيس،
try this that I made.
جرب هذا الذي قمت بصنعه.
Boss.
رئيس.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
What happened? Who ate it?
ماذا حدث؟ من أكله؟
It was you.
لقد كنت أنت.
Which eye of yours saw me eating it?
أية عين منك رأتني آكله؟
I saw everything.
لقد رأيت كل شئ.
Do you have any proof?
هل لديك أي دليل؟
Oh my!
يا إلهي!
Where's my knife?
أين سكيني؟
Dongfang.
دونغفانغ.
Oh, Boss, look at her!
يا رئيس، أنظر إليها!
Look!
ينظر!
Let go of me!
أتركني!
It was you.
لقد كنت أنت.
Hey, stop fighting, you two!
مهلا، توقفوا عن القتال، يا اثنين!
The boss will be back soon.
الرئيس سوف يعود قريبا.
Well,
حسنًا،
I need to fix this rabbit lantern quickly.
أحتاج إلى إصلاح فانوس الأرنب هذا بسرعة.
This is Feiye's
هذا هو فيي
most treasured gift.
الهدية الأكثر قيمة.
Dongfang.
دونغفانغ.
Boss.
رئيس.
Stop drinking.
توقف عن الشرب.
Dongfang,
دونغفانغ،
you're back.
لقد عدت.
Boss,
رئيس،
sneaking food again?
تناول الطعام خلسةً مرةً أخرى؟
Dongfang.
دونغفانغ.
Are you really gone?
هل ذهبت حقا؟
Will you never come back?
هل لن تعود أبدا؟
That's the end of the Monster Inn story.
وهذه نهاية قصة Monster Inn.
Does the Monster Inn from the story
هل نزل الوحش من القصة
really exist?
هل هي موجودة حقا؟
It's just a story.
إنها مجرد قصة.
There are no monsters in this world,
لا يوجد وحوش في هذا العالم،
so naturally there's no Monster Inn.
لذا فمن الطبيعي ألا يكون هناك Monster Inn.
So-called monsters
ما يسمى بالوحوش
are merely
هي مجرد
people trapped by obsessions in their hearts.
الناس محاصرون بالهواجس في قلوبهم.
Obsessions.
الهواجس.